Papers of the National War Labor Board on Microfilm 5752 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Case Files (Selected Cases) continued; Interstaff Communications (Selections) (Reel 19)
  - Summary of the Work Done by Women and the Conditions under Which It Is Done in the Lynn Plant., 1918; 19 (Reel 19)
    November 1918. 7 pp.
  - Classification of Workers in Lynn General Electric Plant., 1918; 20 (Reel 19)
    September 15, 1918. 6 pp.
  - Digest of Testimony on Wages., 21 (Reel 19)
  - Digest of Testimony on Re-Instatement Cases., 1918; 22 (Reel 19)
    September 8, 1918. 41 pp.
  - Summary of Evidence., 1918; 23 (Reel 19)
    October 1918. 24 pp.
  - Transcript of Hearing on Russell and McCobb Re-Instatement Controversy., 1918; 24 (Reel 19)
    November 7, 1918. 57 pp.
  - Examiner's Decision in McCobb and Russell Re-Instatement Case., 1918; 25 (Reel 19)
    November 8, 1918. 1 p.
  - Minutes of Meeting of General Joint Committee on Adjustment., 1918; 26 (Reel 19)
    December 24, 1918. 9 pp.
  - Memorandum on Lynn General Elections.., 1918; 27 (Reel 19)
    November 6, 1918 3 pp.
  - Report on Committee Elections., 1919; 28 (Reel 19)
    January 23, 1919. 5 pp.
  - Memorandum on the Value of Data relating to Shop Committee Systems by F.H. Bird., 1919; 29 (Reel 19)
    January 8, 1919. 1 p.
  - Data relating to Shop Committee System., 1918; 30 (Reel 19)
    September-December 1918. 41 pp.
  - Announcement of Completion of Lynn Adjustment by the General Joint Committee on Adjustment., 1918; 31 (Reel 19)
    March 5, 1919. 5 pp.
  - Selected Correspondence., 1918-1919; 32 (Reel 19)
    August 1918-March 1919. 17 pp.
  - William C. Aborn, Examiner in Charge, Report from Bridgeport., 1919; 33 (Reel 19)
    April 5, 1919. 2 pp.
  - Herbert B. Brougham, Special Agent, Proposal to Study the British Cooperative Wholesale and Retail System., 1918; 34 (Reel 19)
    October 1918. 5 pp.
  - Elisabeth Christman, Chief of Women Field Investigators, Interstaff Correspondence File., 35 (Reel 19)
    59 pp.
  - William P. Harvey, Chief Investigator, Interstaff Correspondence File., 36 (Reel 19)
    79 pp.
  - Antone Johannsen, Investigator, Interstaff Correspondence File., 37 (Reel 19)
  - C.E. Michael, Employer Member of the Board, Interstaff Correspondence File., 38 (Reel 19)
  - Marie Obenauer, Chief Woman Administrator, Interstaff Correspondence File., 39 (Reel 19)
  - William F. Ogburn, Interstaff Correspondence File., 40 (Reel 19)
  - Loyall A. Osburne, Employer Member of the Board, Interstaff Correspondence File., 41 (Reel 19)
  - Charles P. Sweeney, Press Release Writer, Interstaff Correspondence File., 42 (Reel 19)
  - Frank P. Walsh, Joint Chairman of the Board, Interstaff Correspondence File., 43 (Reel 19)
- Administrative Files (Selections), General Subject Files (Selections), Executive Session Minutes--Supplement (Reel 20)
  - Summary of Awards to the National War Labor Board., 1 (Reel 20)
    52 pp.
  - Index and Checklist to Awards and Finding., 2 (Reel 20)
  - Press Releases: Dated Press Releases., 1918; 3 (Reel 20)
    May 6-August 28, 1918. 122 pp.
  - Dated Press Releases., 1919; 4 (Reel 20)
    November 20, 1918-March 21, 1919. 50 pp.
  - Press Releases of Original Complaints, by Docket Number., 5 (Reel 20)
    66 pp.
  - Principles and Policies: Statement of Principles and Rules of Procedure., 1919; 6 (Reel 20)
  - Essay on the Policies of the National War Labor Board., 7 (Reel 20)
  - The National War Labor Board: What it is, How it works., 8 (Reel 20)
  - Statement of Principles and Policies Submitted by the Representatives of the Employers., 1918; 9 (Reel 20)
    March 6, 1918. 2 pp.
  - Memorandum respecting the Interpretation of the "Principles" of the National War Labor Board as Applied to the So-Called "Non-Union Establishment" by Loyall A. Osborne., 10 (Reel 20)
  - Correspondence with the League for Industrial Rights., 11 (Reel 20)
  - Loyall A. Osborne to William H. Taft, May 31, 1918. Letter Stating Employer Member's Fear of Unionization., 12 (Reel 20)
  - Publications: Proclamation of the President of the United States Creating the National War Labor Board: Its Functions and Powers, Principles Governing Industry, and Method of Presenting Complaints and Procedures., 1918; 13 (Reel 20)
  - Memorandum ont eh minimum Wage and Increased Cost of Living., 1918; 14 (Reel 20)
    July 12, 1918. 80 pp.
  - Women in Industry: Industrial Justice for Women (Work of the National War Labor Board on Behalf of Women)., 15 (Reel 20)
  - Present Economic Status of Women, New York Times Clipping., 1918; 16 (Reel 20)
    October 6, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Awards Known to Concern Women Workers., 17 (Reel 20)
  - Report of Working Conditions for Women in Corn Products Refining Company., 18 (Reel 20)
  - Report on the Displacement of Men by Women in the Schenectady Plant of General Electric, Data Collected under the Direction of Marie Obenauer., 1918; 19 (Reel 20)
    July 17, 1918. 14 pp.
  - Effect of the First Draft on Financial Responsibility of Women at Lynn Plant of General Electric., 20 (Reel 20)
  - "Wages, Rates, and Earnings of Women Employees for 1915 and 1918 at Lynn Plant of General Electric and as Compared to Men in Same Occupations" by Caroline E. Wilson., 21 (Reel 20)
    September 1918. 8 pp.
  - Proceedings of Conference of Trade Union Women., 1918; 22 (Reel 20)
    October 4-5, 1918. 35 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 23 (Reel 20)
    May 10, 1918. AM. 80 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 24 (Reel 20)
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 25 (Reel 20)
    June 1, 1918. AM. 86 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 26 (Reel 20)
    September 11, 1918. PM. 18 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 27 (Reel 20)
    September 12, 1918. PM. 5 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 28 (Reel 20)
    September 13, 1918. AM. 3 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 29 (Reel 20)
    September 13, 1918. PM. 130 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 30 (Reel 20)
    September 17, 1918. AM. 18 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 31 (Reel 20)
    September 24, 1918. PM. 78 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 32 (Reel 20)
    September 25, 1918. PM. 6 pp.
- Executive Session Minutes--Supplement continued; Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board: Executive Session Minutes (Reel 21)
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 1 (Reel 21)
    September 26, 1918. AM. 74 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 2 (Reel 21)
    September 27, 1918. AM. 52 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 3 (Reel 21)
    September 27, 1918. PM. 49 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 4 (Reel 21)
    October 11, 1918. AM. 89 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 5 (Reel 21)
    October 15, 1918. AM. 28 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1918; 6 (Reel 21)
    December 20, 1918. AM. 26 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1919; 7 (Reel 21)
    January 21, 1919. PM. 99 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1919; 8 (Reel 21)
    March 27, 1919. PM. 65 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1919; 9 (Reel 21)
    April 8, 1919. AM. 40 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1919; 10 (Reel 21)
    April 8, 1919. PM. 3 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1919; 11 (Reel 21)
    April 9, 1919. AM. 60 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1919; 12 (Reel 21)
    April 9, 1919. PM. 101 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1919; 13 (Reel 21)
    April 10, 1919. PM. 104 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1919; 14 (Reel 21)
    April 11, 1919. PM. 113 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1919; 15 (Reel 21)
    April 29, 1919. AM. 51 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1919; 16 (Reel 21)
    April 30, 1919. AM. 36 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes, 1919; 17 (Reel 21)
    April 30, 1919. PM. 10 pp.
  - Executive Session Minutes. Summary Minutes., 1919; 18 (Reel 21)
    April 29-June 25, 1919. 53 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 19 (Reel 21)
    February 25, 1918. 3 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 20 (Reel 21)
    February 26, 1918. 7 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 21 (Reel 21)
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 22 (Reel 21)
    March 12, 1918. 1 p.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 23 (Reel 21)
    April 16, 1918. 1 p.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 24 (Reel 21)
    May 8, 9, and 10, 1918. 10 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 25 (Reel 21)
    May 11, 1918. 3 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 26 (Reel 21)
    May 13, 1918. 1 p.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 27 (Reel 21)
    May 14, 1918. 1 p.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 28 (Reel 21)
    May 21, 1918. 3 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 29 (Reel 21)
    May 22, 1918. 2 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 30 (Reel 21)
    May 27, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 31 (Reel 21)
    June 1, 1918. 8 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 32 (Reel 21)
    June 12, 1918. 7 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 33 (Reel 21)
    June 27, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 34 (Reel 21)
    June 28, 1918. 10 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 35 (Reel 21)
    July 9, 1918. 6 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 36 (Reel 21)
    July 10, 1918. 6 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 37 (Reel 21)
    July 11, 1918. 6 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 38 (Reel 21)
    July 12, 1918. 10 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 39 (Reel 21)
    July 23, 1918. 2 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 40 (Reel 21)
    July 24, 1918. 2 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 41 (Reel 21)
    July 25, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 42 (Reel 21)
    July 26, 1918. 3 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 43 (Reel 21)
    July 30, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 44 (Reel 21)
    July 31, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 45 (Reel 21)
    August 1, 1918. 1 p.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 46 (Reel 21)
    August 13, 1918. 5 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 47 (Reel 21)
    August 14, 1918. 1 p.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 48 (Reel 21)
    August 15, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 49 (Reel 21)
    August 16, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 50 (Reel 21)
    August 21, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 51 (Reel 21)
    August 27, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 52 (Reel 21)
    August 28, 1918. 5 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 53 (Reel 21)
    September 10, 1918. 3 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 54 (Reel 21)
    September 11, 1918. 5 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 55 (Reel 21)
    September 12, 1918. 2 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 56 (Reel 21)
    September 13, 1918. 3 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 57 (Reel 21)
    September 17, 1918. 2 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 58 (Reel 21)
    September 24, 1918. 3 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 59 (Reel 21)
    September 26, 1918. 3 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 60 (Reel 21)
    September 27, 1918. 6 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 61 (Reel 21)
    October 3, 1918. 3 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 62 (Reel 21)
    October 9, 1918. 6 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 63 (Reel 21)
    October 10, 1918. 4 pp.
  - Minutes of Public Meetings of the National War Labor Board, 1918; 64 (Reel 21)
    October 11, 1918. 2 pp.
- Digests of Cases (Reel 22)
  - American Federation of Labor v. Tennessee Coal, Iron, and Railroad et al. Birmingham, AL., 1 (Reel 22)
  - Industrial Workers et al v. Employers Association et al. St. Louis, MO., 2 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 14 v. War Department. San Antonio, TX, 3 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 101 v. American Propellor and Manufacturing. Baltimore, MD, 4 (Reel 22)
  - Porto Rico Agricultural Workers v. Employers. Porto Rico., 5 (Reel 22)
  - Industrial Workers v. Employers. Oshkosh, WI., 6 (Reel 22)
  - Paper Makers, Local 68 et al. v. Harley Pulp and Paper et al. Portland, OR., 7 (Reel 22)
  - Marine Workers Affiliation v. Boat Owners. new York City., 8 (Reel 22)
  - Musical Instrument Makers, Local 1 v. Lyon and Healy. Chicago., 9 (Reel 22)
  - Miners' Union, Local 268 v. Thomas Iron. Wharton, NJ., 10 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Worthington Pump and Machinery. East Cambridge, MA., 11 (Reel 22)
  - United Hatters v. United States Hat. Danbury, CT., 12 (Reel 22)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Local 226 v. St. Joseph Lead. Herculaneum, MO., 13 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Machine Shops. Bridgeport, CT, 14 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Eugene Dietzgen. Chicago, 15 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. General Electric. Pittsfield, MA, 16 (Reel 22)
  - Cranemen v. General Electric. Schenectady, NY, 17 (Reel 22)
  - Federal Labor Union 15543 et al. v. Hammond Lumber et al. Van Buren, ME., 18 (Reel 22)
  - Steam Engineers, Local 45 et al. v. Joplin and Pittsburg Railway. Joplin, MO, and Pittsburg, KS., 19 (Reel 22)
  - Building Trades v. Bullard Machine et al. Bridgeport, CT, 20 (Reel 22)
  - Tin Plate Employees, local 31 v. Employers. Elwood, IN, 21 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 477 v. Philadelphia Rapid Transit. Philadelphia., 22 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Koken Barber Supply. St. Louis, MO., 23 (Reel 22)
  - Dredgermen's Union v. Employers. San Francisco, 24 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters District Council v. General Builders Association. Detroit, MI., 25 (Reel 22)
  - Elevator Constructors Union v. Electrical Workers. Chicago, 26 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 268 v. Cleveland Railway. Cleveland, OH., 27 (Reel 22)
  - Polishers v. Remington Arms. Bridgeport, CT, 28 (Reel 22)
  - Molders v. Phoenix Manufacturing. Eau Claire, WI, 29 (Reel 22)
  - Paper Makers et al. v. International Paper et al. New York City., 30 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 178 v. Avery Company. Peoria, IL., 31 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 818 et al. v. Wheeling Mold and Foundry et al. Wheeling, WV., 32 (Reel 22)
  - Painters, District Council 14 v. Cuthbert Boat. Chicago, 33 (Reel 22)
  - Iron Workers v. Du Pont Engineering. Nashville, TN., 34 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists et al. v. Frick Company et al. Waynesboro, PA, 35 (Reel 22)
  - Aurora, Elgin, and Chicago Railroad v. Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 215. Aurora, IL, 36 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 168 v. Scranton Railway. Scranton, PA., 37 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 125, 236 and 805 v. East St. Louis and Suburban Railway et al. East St. Louis., 38 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 576 v. Schenectady Railway. Schenectady, NY., 39 (Reel 22)
  - Electrical Workers v. Northern Indiana Gas and Electric. Hammond, IN, 40 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Virginia Bridge and Iron. Roanoke, VA., 41 (Reel 22)
  - Master Plumbers v. Plumbers, Gas, and Steam Fitters, Local 41. Butte, MT, 42 (Reel 22)
  - Standard Boiler and Plate Iron v. Boilermakers and Helpers, Local 363. East St. Louis, IL and Niles, OH, 43 (Reel 22)
  - Plumbers and Steam Fitters, Local 149 v. Reliable Heating and Plumbing et al. Champaign and Urbana, IL, 44 (Reel 22)
  - Hosiery Workers, Local 696 v. Henry Brown Hosiery et al. Philadelphia, 45 (Reel 22)
  - Cleveland Osborn Manufacturing v. Cleveland Building Trades. Cleveland, OH, 46 (Reel 22)
  - Stove Mounters, Local 8 v. Estate Stove. Hamilton, OH., 47 (Reel 22)
  - Jurisdictional Dispute in Cigar Makers' Council. New York City, 48 (Reel 22)
  - Sheffield Iron v. Employees. Sheffield, AL., 49 (Reel 22)
  - Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers v. Kingsport Fiber et al. Kingsport, TN@ Bristol and Buena Vista, VA., 50 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 380 v. Cleveland, Southwestern and Columbus Railway. Elyria, OH, 51 (Reel 22)
  - Bridge and Iron Workers, Local 214 et al. v. Fort Pitt Bridge Works. Canonsburg, PA., 52 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 241 and 308 v. Chicago Surface Lines et al. Chicago., 53 (Reel 22)
  - Coopers, Local 193 v. Wooden Tank Manufacturers. Chicago., 54 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. American Locomotive. Schenectady, NY., 55 (Reel 22)
  - Painters, Local 47 et al. v. Master House Painters et al. Indianapolis, 56 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, District Lodge 1 v. Hess Bright manufacturing. Philadelphia, 57 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 198 v. General Contractors. Dallas, TX, 58 (Reel 22)
  - Journeymen Bookbinders, Local 4 v. US Government Printing Office. Washington, DC, 59 (Reel 22)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Policemen's Benevolent Association v. Pennsylvania Railroad Police Department. New York Division, 60 (Reel 22)
  - Building Construction Employers Association v. Steam and Operating Engineers. Chicago, 61 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Nordyke and Marmon. Indianapolis., 62 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Public Service Railway. Newark, NJ., 63 (Reel 22)
  - Boatmen v. Owners of Steamboat Alabama of the Old Bay Line. Baltimore, MD, 64 (Reel 22)
  - Boilermakers, Local 592 v. Kansas City Structural Steel et al. Tulsa, OK, 65 (Reel 22)
  - Portland Railway, Light and Power v. Street and Electric Railway Employees. Leetonia, OH, 66 (Reel 22)
  - Lever Brothers v. Carpenters District Council. Boston, 67 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Elyria and Cleveland Railroad. Cleveland, OH, 68 (Reel 22)
  - Bridge, Structural, and Ornamental Iron Workers, Locals 35 and 40 v. Iron League Erectors' Association. New York City., 69 (Reel 22)
  - Crafts Affiliated with the Michigan Federation of Labor v. Packard Motor Car. Detroit, 70 (Reel 22)
  - Crafts Affiliated with the Michigan Federation of Labor v. Lincoln Motor Car. Detroit, 71 (Reel 22)
  - Cold Storage Warehouse Workers v. Pier House et al. Chicago, 72 (Reel 22)
  - Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen v. Western Cold Storage et al. Chicago, 73 (Reel 22)
  - Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 566 v. Wilson Provision et al. Peoria, IL, 74 (Reel 22)
  - Sheep Shearers, Fremont County Wyoming v. J.M. Wilson, Wool Grower. Douglas, WY, 75 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 735 v. Jacksonville Traction. Jacksonville, FL, 76 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 528 v. United States. Washington, DC, 77 (Reel 22)
  - Electrical v. T.A. Gillespie Company. South Amboy, NJ., 78 (Reel 22)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 429 v. Du Pont Powder. Nashville, TN, 79 (Reel 22)
  - Chicago Foundrymen's Association v. Molders. Chicago., 80 (Reel 22)
  - Flour Mill Employees Union 15974 v. Pittsburg Elevator et al. Pittsburg, KS, 81 (Reel 22)
  - Cooks, Waiters, and Waitresses, Local 748 v. Sundry Proprietors of Cafes and Restaurants. Fort Worth, TX, 82 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Mark Manufacturing. Evanston, IL., 83 (Reel 22)
  - Journeymen Masons v. Employers. West Point, NY, 84 (Reel 22)
  - Merchant and Evans v. Union Machinists. Philadelphia, PA, 85 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 802 v. Kansas City and Western Railway. Leavenworth, KS, 86 (Reel 22)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. Southern California Iron and Steel. Los Angeles., 87 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Willys-Overland. Elyria, OH, 88 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 132 and 148 v. United Traction. Albany, NY, 89 (Reel 22)
  - Boilermakers et al. v. National Refining. Coffeyville, KS., 90 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 194 v. New Orleans Railway and Light. New Orleans, LA., 91 (Reel 22)
  - Fine Department v. City of St. Louis. St. Louis, MO, 92 (Reel 22)
  - Electrical workers, Local 465 v. Employers. San Diego, 93 (Reel 22)
  - Bricklayers v. Hampton and Company. San Deigo, 94 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Philadelphia Belting. Philadelphia, 95 (Reel 22)
  - Building Trades Employers' Association v. Hod Carriers, Building, and Common Laborers, Local 10. Cleveland, OH., 96 (Reel 22)
  - Printing Pressmen and Assistants, Local 4 v. Franklin Division of Franklin-Typothetae. Chicago., 97 (Reel 22)
  - Federal Labor Union 16104 v. Emerson Brantingham Manufacturing et al. Batavia, IL., 98 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 108 v. Bethlehem Shipbuilding. Fore River Yards, 99 (Reel 22)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Local 266 v. Trenton Smelter and Refining. Trenton, NJ, 100 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 515 v. Galesburg Railway, Lighting, and Power. Galesburg, IL., 101 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Red Star Milling et al. Wichita, KS, 102 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 64 v. Mason Machine Works. Taunton, MA., 103 (Reel 22)
  - Oil Field Workers Union 15940 v. Employers. Montebello, CA, 104 (Reel 22)
  - Masters, Mates and Pilots v. Cornell Shipbuilding. Camden, NJ, 105 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Lowell Gas and Light. Lowell, MA, 106 (Reel 22)
  - Molder, Local 244 v. Central Specialty Company et al. Detroit, MI., 107 (Reel 22)
  - Bookbinders, Local 7 v. US Government Printing Office. Washington, DC, 108 (Reel 22)
  - General Strike. Bloomington, IL, 109 (Reel 22)
  - Foundry Workers v. Employers. Detroit, 110 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 244 v. US Department of the Interior. Grand Junction, CO, 111 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 282, 580, and 532 v. New York State Railways. Rochester, NY, 112 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Hamilton Machine Tool. Hamilton, OH, 113 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 330 v. Russell Motor Car. Buffalo, NY., 114 (Reel 22)
  - Hydraulic Press Manufacturing Company v. Babcock and Wilcox Company et al. Barberton, OH, 115 (Reel 22)
  - Central Labor Union v. Price Fireproofing. Poughkeepsie, NY, 116 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Suwanee Iron Company. Russellville, AL., 117 (Reel 22)
  - Federal Labor Union 15338 v. Magnolia Petroleum Company. Beaumont, TX, 118 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. General Electric. Schenectady, NY, 119 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 218 v. Cleveland Steel Castings et al. Cleveland, OH., 120 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 1 v. Midvale Steel. Philadelphia, 121 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Pennsylvania-New Jersey Railway. Trenton, NJ, 122 (Reel 22)
  - Electrical Linemen, Local 30 v. Erie Lighting Company et al. Erie PA., 123 (Reel 22)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. A.M. Byers. Girard, OH, 124 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Salt Lake Iron and Steel. Salt Lake City, UT, 125 (Reel 22)
  - Building Trades Employers Association. Chicago, 126 (Reel 22)